(Leonard:)What?
It's a Pokémon reference.
(Woman:)I don't know what that means.
(Sheldon:)Well, we gave it a shot.
(Sheldon:)How about you?
(Older woman:)I'm married,
and I'm her grandmother.
(Sheldon:)Ah, what might have been.
(Sheldon:)And you, give my regards
to Barnum and Bailey.
(Bernadette:)Stuart took that rejection
like a pro.
(Penny:)Well, he knew
he was on the breast cam.
I don't have much practice
turning men down.
(Amy:)It wasn't so much fun.
(Bernadette:)Oh, you get used to it.
(Bernadette:)Some guys you have
to turn down over and over.
(Penny:)And sometimes
we marry them anyway.
(phone chimes)
(Amy(Phone text sound):)Huh.
(Amy(Phone text sound):)Well, this is weird.
(Leonard:)What?
Barry Kripke just asked me out.
(gasps)
BERNADETTE: Oh.
(Bernadette:)Look at you...
two guys in one day!
(Penny:)I told you things would change
if you plucked your eyebrows!